favit.com 2011-04-16

# 

loading...

favit processes your personal data in conformity with this privacy policy and with the strict rules of European data protection legislation.

This privacy policy is a part of our Terms & Conditions and should be read carefully, as it specifies which rights you have and how you can exercise your rights. Any use of the website implies the entire acceptance of this privacy policy.

### Types of personal data we collect

  * **Public information uploaded by you:**
    * information in your profile, pictures, links, third party web service accounts
    * general comments, comments sent to other users, as well as ratings, shares, reshares, saves
    * links to your friends and streams
  * **Private information uploaded by you:**
    * settings and administrative data such as your username and password,
    * your privacy settings, settings of created stream, skins and sources
  * **History and logs**
    * time, date and URL of all favit pages visited by you
    * the URL of the shared websites
    * the searches your perform on the website
    * technical information regarding your internet browser and computer

### Purposes for which we use your personal data

  * **We use your personal data to:**
    * publish the information intended to be made public by you, under the conditions specified in your privacy settings
    * allow you to correctly use the website in accordance with your settings
    * perform general customer administration
    * send you communications about the website
    * provide you with advertisements tailored to your profile
    * investigate fraud and infringements of our Code of Conduct
    * generate anonymous statistics about the (users of the) website, to improve the website or convey statistical information to third parties

### Storage term and location

  * **favit applies the following storage terms** :
    * Information uploaded by you: stored during a period of 6 months after you delete this information, or delete your account.
    * History and logs: stored during a period of 6 months after the history item or log event was created
    * Cookies: cookies used on the website have a maximum lifetime of 100 days.

Your personal data may be stored in a country outside the EU.

**Contact information**  
favit Network B.V.  
WTC Amsterdam, Tower C-11  
Strawinskylaan 1143  
1077XX Amsterdam  
The Netherlands   
Phone: + (31) 20 578 8386   
Fax: + (31) 20 578 8389
